<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Social Supplements (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.SocialSupplements</packageId>
  <author>pelador</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/SocialSupplements</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>Mlie.MedicalSupplements</packageId>
      <displayName>Medical Supplements</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2195037369</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/emipa606/MedicalSupplements/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Mlie.Fermenter</li>
    <li>Mlie.MedicalSupplements</li>
    <li>Mlie.Apothecary</li>
    <li>Crustypeanut.RC2.Core</li>
    <li>notfood.SeedsPlease</li>
    <li>bishop.smokeleafindustryreborn</li>
    <li>VanillaExpanded.VCookE</li>
    <li>dismarzero.VGP.VGPVegetableGarden</li>
    <li>dismarzero.VGP.VGPGardenMedicine</li>
    <li>VanillaExpanded.VPlantsE</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>Update of peladors mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2005917068

[img]https://i.imgur.com/GYswkZ7.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/SocialSupplements
	
--- Original Description ---
Overview

Optional Expansion for Medical Supplements: Adds social items for use.

(Note this mod is dependant on the Medical Supplements mod to work.)


Details

The following PDF document provides an understanding what this mod offers:

Social Supplements Notes
https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?url=https://1drv.ms/b/s!Au3GsmKyQkDYispEPTdxW3va6zdhcQ?e=ScmDw1


Mod Notes

There are mood alterations associated with the above drugs as relevant and in keeping with a vanilla theme as best as possible, whilst still allowing for refinement.

Research projects associated and bulk recipes provided.

Mod option to vary the base research costs by a percentage level.

Bulk recipes for the vanilla drugs: Pekoe tea, flake, yayo, go-juice, wake-up and smokeleaf joints have been added.

Save compatible (Note: You will need to reassign new drug policies if part way through a savegame to schedule the use of the above SS drugs) and mod friendly. To remove the mod you would have to remove all items introduced first.

Recommended

Drug Policy Fix; can be used to help manage and correct drugs added or removed part way through a save game. It will also sort the drug listings alphabetically.
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2195390245

Compatability Notes
*** Subject to conversion ***

Apothecary - Can make Cayenne pepper powder, which doesn't spoil, can be used in food recipes and to make hot sauce.
RimCuisine V1.2: Will use fruits and fungi in recipes.
RimCuisine 2: Will use fruits and fungi in recipes. Will use chilli peppers to make hot sauce.
Seeds Please - includes patch support to generate seeds/shoots/spores for plants used in this mod.
Smokeleaf Industry - Vaping products will additionally use Buds in their recipes.
Smokeleaf Industry Reborn - Vaping products will additionally use Buds in their recipes.
VCE/VPE - fruits, peppers and other items will be used in applicable recipes.
VGP Vegetable Garden: Will use fruits and mushroom in recipes. (Best putting VGP Garden before supplement mods).
VGP Garden Medicine - Some vanilla bulk recipes are not added due to potential duplication.


Credits

Some artwork revisions by Oskar Potocki.

Chinese (Simplified) translation by Maxwell.J

(CC BY-NC-SA 4.0)</description>
</ModMetaData>